Finding Aid for the Office of the Chancellor. Administrative files of Charles E. Young. UARC.0594
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Index: JD1/04L6. Governmental Relations-Los Angeles City-1984 Olympics-Los Angeles Olympics Organizing Committee-CEY as Member-Citizens Advisory Commission., 1979-1984. (Box 91, Folder 9)
- Index: JD1/04L6. Governmental Relations-Los Angeles City-1984 Olympics-Los Angeles Olympics Organizing Committee-CEY as Member-LAOOC Newsletters., 1981-1982. (Box 92, Folder 1)
- Index: JD1/04L6. Governmental Relations-Los Angeles City-1984 Olympics-Los Angeles Olympics Organizing Committee-CEY as Member-Olympic Rose., Undated. (Box 92, Folder 10)
- Index: JD1/04L6. Governmental Relations-Los Angeles City-1984 Olympics-Los Angeles Olympics Organizing Committee-Meetings #6., 1985-1986. (Box 92, Folder 11)
- Index: JD1/04L6. Governmental Relations-Los Angeles City-1984 Olympics-Los Angeles Olympics Organizing Committee-Meetings #5., 1983-1984. (Box 92, Folder 12)
- Index: JD1/04L6. Governmental Relations-Los Angeles City-1984 Olympics-Los Angeles Olympics Organizing Committee-Meetings #4., 1982-1983. (Box 92, Folder 13)
- Index: JD1/04L6. Governmental Relations-Los Angeles City-1984 Olympics-Los Angeles Olympics Organizing Committee-CEY as Member-Commissioners., 1979-1982. (Box 92, Folder 2)
- Index: JD1/04L6. Governmental Relations-Los Angeles City-1984 Olympics-Los Angeles Olympics Organizing Committee-CEY as Member-So. Cal. Cte. for the Olympic Games., 1977-1982. (Box 92, Folder 3)
- Index: JD1/04L6. Governmental Relations-Los Angeles City-1984 Olympics-Los Angeles Olympics Organizing Committee-CEY as Member-LAOOC Faculty Club Membership., 1981. (Box 92, Folder 4)
- Index: JD1/04L6. Governmental Relations-Los Angeles City-1984 Olympics-Los Angeles Olympics Organizing Committee-CEY as Member-Citizen Savings Hall of Fame., 1981. (Box 92, Folder 5)
- Index: JD1/04L6. Governmental Relations-Los Angeles City-1984 Olympics-Los Angeles Olympics Organizing Committee-CEY as Member-LAOOC Youth Commission., 1980. (Box 92, Folder 6)
- Index: JD1/04L6. Governmental Relations-Los Angeles City-1984 Olympics-Los Angeles Olympics Organizing Committee-CEY as Member-LAOOC Articles of Incorporation, Bylaws., 1978-1979. (Box 92, Folder 7)
- Index: JD1/04L6. Governmental Relations-Los Angeles City-1984 Olympics-Los Angeles Olympics Organizing Committee-CEY as Member-Olympic Charter., 1978-1979. (Box 92, Folder 8)
- Index: JD1/04L6. Governmental Relations-Los Angeles City-1984 Olympics-Los Angeles Olympics Organizing Committee-CEY as Member-Int'l Amateur Athletic Foundation Handbk., 1977-1978. (Box 92, Folder 9)
- Index: BL4/A20. Systemwide Administration-Planning & Analysis-Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning-Academic Planning & Program Review-Organized Research., 1988. (Box 93, Folder 1)
- Index: BL4/A20. Systemwide Administration-Planning & Analysis-Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning-Academic Planning & Program Review-Organized Research., 1987. (Box 93, Folder 2)
- Index: BL4/A20. Systemwide Administration-Planning & Analysis-Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning-Academic Planning & Program Review-Organized Research., 1981. (Box 93, Folder 3)
- Index: BL4/A20. Systemwide Administration-Planning & Analysis-Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning-Academic Planning & Program Review-Organized Research., 1980. (Box 93, Folder 4)
- Index: BL4/A2U. Systemwide Administration-Planning & Analysis-Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning-Academic Planning & Program Review-Univ. Acad. Plan., 1986. (Box 93, Folder 5)
- Index: BL4/A2U. Systemwide Administration-Planning & Analysis-Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning-Academic Planning & Program Review-Univ. Acad. Plan., 1985. (Box 93, Folder 6)
- Index: BL4/A2U. Systemwide Administration-Planning & Analysis-Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning-Academic Planning & Program Review-Org. Research. #2., 1984. (Box 94, Folder 1)
- Index: BL4/A2U. Systemwide Administration-Planning & Analysis-Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning-Academic Planning & Program Review-Org. Research. #1., 1984. (Box 94, Folder 2)
- Index: BL4/A2U. Systemwide Administration-Planning & Analysis-Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning-Academic Planning & Program Review-Organized Research., 1983. (Box 94, Folder 3)
- Index: BL4/A2U. Systemwide Administration-Planning & Analysis-Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning-Academic Planning & Program Review-Organized Research., 1981. (Box 94, Folder 4)
- Index: BL4/A2U. Systemwide Administration-Planning & Analysis-Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning-Academic Planning & Program Review-Organized Research., 1980. (Box 94, Folder 5)
- Index: BL4/A2. Systemwide Administration-Planning & Analysis-Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning-Coord. of Acad., Phys. & Fiscal Planning-APPRB., 1990. (Box 95, Folder 1)
- Index: BL4/A2. Systemwide Administration-Planning & Analysis-Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning-Coord. of Acad., Phys. & Fiscal Planning-APPRB., 1988. (Box 95, Folder 2)
- Index: BL4/A2. Systemwide Administration-Planning & Analysis-Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning-Coord. of Acad., Phys. & Fiscal Planning-APPRB., 1988. (Box 95, Folder 3)
- Index: BL4/A2U. Systemwide Administration-Planning & Analysis-Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning-Academic Planning & Program Review-Univ. Acad. Plan., 1975-1977. (Box 95, Folder 4)
- Index: BL4/A2U. Systemwide Administration-Planning & Analysis-Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning-Academic Planning & Program Review-Univ. Acad. Plan., 1973-1974. (Box 95, Folder 5)
- Index: BL4/C3. Systemwide Administration-Planning & Analysis-Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning-Campus Program & Performance Review., 1971. (Box 95, Folder 6)
- Index: BL4/J6. Systemwide Administration-Planning & Analysis-Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning-Joint Planning Group., 1979. (Box 95, Folder 7)
- Index: BL4/J6. Systemwide Administration-Planning & Analysis-Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning-Joint Planning Group., 1979. (Box 95, Folder 8)
- Index: JD1/04L6. Governmental Relations-Los Angeles City-1984 Olympics-Los Angeles Olympics Organizing Committee-Meetings #3., 1981-1982. (Box 96, Folder 1)
- Index: JD1/04L6. Governmental Relations-Los Angeles City-1984 Olympics-Los Angeles Olympics Organizing Committee-Meetings #2., 1979-1981. (Box 96, Folder 2)
- Index: JD1/04L6. Governmental Relations-Los Angeles City-1984 Olympics-Los Angeles Olympics Organizing Committee-Meetings #1., 1979. (Box 96, Folder 3)
- Index: JD1/04L6. Governmental Relations-Los Angeles City-1984 Olympics-Los Angeles Olympics Organizing Committee-Olympics Cte. Reports #3 (1 of 2)., 1984-1985. (Box 96, Folder 4)
- Index: JD1/04L6. Governmental Relations-Los Angeles City-1984 Olympics-Los Angeles Olympics Organizing Committee-Olympics Cte. Reports #3 (2 of 2)., 1983. (Box 96, Folder 5)
- Index: JD1/04L6. Governmental Relations-Los Angeles City-1984 Olympics-Los Angeles Olympics Organizing Committee-Olympics Cte. Reports #2., 1982. (Box 97, Folder 1)
- Index: VH94/E2. Instructional Units-Health Sciences, Center for-Public Health, School of-Ecuador DEIDS Project., 1974. (Box 97, Folder 10)
- Index: VH94/G4. Instructional Units-Health Sciences, Center for-Public Health, School of-Ghana., 1973-1979. (Box 97, Folder 11)
- Index: JD1/04L6. Governmental Relations-Los Angeles City-1984 Olympics-Los Angeles Olympics Organizing Committee-Olympics Cte. Reports #1 (1 of 2)., 1981-1982. (Box 97, Folder 2)
- Index: JD1/04L6. Governmental Relations-Los Angeles City-1984 Olympics-Los Angeles Olympics Organizing Committee-Olympics Cte. Reports #1 (2 of 2)., 1979-1980. (Box 97, Folder 3)
- Index: JD1/04L6. Governmental Relations-Los Angeles City-1984 Olympics-Los Angeles Olympics Organizing Committee-Membership., 1979-1984. (Box 97, Folder 4)
- Index: JD1/04L6. Governmental Relations-Los Angeles City-1984 Olympics-Los Angeles Olympics Organizing Committee-Visitor Relations Advisory Committee-Volunteer Program., 1980-1984. (Box 97, Folder 5)
- Index: JD1/04L6. Governmental Relations-Los Angeles City-1984 Olympics-Los Angeles Olympics Organizing Committee-Visitor Relations Advisory Committee., 1980-1983. (Box 97, Folder 6)
- Index: JD1/04L6. Governmental Relations-Los Angeles City-1984 Olympics-Los Angeles Olympics Organizing Committee-Moscow Games., 1979-1980. (Box 97, Folder 7)
- Index: VH94/C6. Instructional Units-Health Sciences, Center for-Public Health, School of-Copenhagen (Proposal for UC-U. of Copenhagen Center for Child Care...)., 1973. (Box 97, Folder 8)
- Index: VH94/D4. Instructional Units-Health Sciences, Center for-Public Health, School of-Degree Programs., 1952-1984. (Box 97, Folder 9)
- Index: VH94/G4D. Instructional Units-Health Sciences, Center for-Public Health, School of-Ghana-Danfa Rural Health Project., 1976-1983. (Box 98, Folder 1)
- Index: VH94/G4D. Instructional Units-Health Sciences, Center for-Public Health, School of-Ghana-Danfa Rural Health Project., 1972-1975. (Box 98, Folder 2)
- Index: VH94/G4D. Instructional Units-Health Sciences, Center for-Public Health, School of-Ghana-Danfa Rural Health Project., 1970-1972. (Box 98, Folder 3)
- Index: VH94/G4D. Instructional Units-Health Sciences, Center for-Public Health, School of-Ghana-Danfa Rural Health Project., 1965-1970. (Box 98, Folder 4)
- Index: VH94/G4M. Instructional Units-Health Sciences, Center for-Public Health, School of-Ghana-Danfa Rural Health Project., 1974-1975. (Box 98, Folder 5)
- Index: X33/C6R4-I. Organized Research-Other Organized Research-Council on Int'l & Comp. Studies- Relations. w/ int'l organizations-Iran., 1976. (Box 99, Folder 1)
- Index: X33/C6R4-I. Organized Research-Other Organized Research-Council on Int'l & Comp. Studies- Relations. w/ int'l organizations-Iran., 1975. (Box 99, Folder 2)
- Index: X33/C6R4-I. Organized Research-Other Organized Research-Council on Int'l & Comp. Studies- Relations. w/ int'l organizations-Iran., 1975. (Box 99, Folder 3)
- Index: X33/C6R4-I. Organized Research-Other Organized Research-Council on Int'l & Comp. Studies- Relations. w/ int'l organizations-Iran., 1975. (Box 99, Folder 4)
- Index: X33/C6R4-N. Organized Research-Other Organized Research-Council on Int'l & Comp. Studies- Relations. w/ int'l organizations-Nigeria., 1982-1994. (Box 99, Folder 5)
- Index: X33/C6R4-N. Organized Research-Other Organized Research-Council on Int'l & Comp. Studies- Relations. w/ int'l organizations-Nigeria., 1980-1981. (Box 99, Folder 6)
- Index: X33/C6R4-T. Organized Research-Other Organized Research-Council on Int'l & Comp. Studies- Relations. w/ int'l organizations-Taiwan., 1987-1993. (Box 99, Folder 7)
- Index: X33/C6R4-T. Organized Research-Other Organized Research-Council on Int'l & Comp. Studies- Relations. w/ int'l organizations-Taiwan., 1979-1986. (Box 99, Folder 8)
- Index: X33/C6R4-Y. Organized Research-Other Organized Research-Council on Int'l & Comp. Studies- Relations. w/ int'l organizations-Yugoslavia., 1994. (Box 99, Folder 9)
- Index: X33/C6R4-Y. Organized Research-Other Organized Research-Council on Int'l & Comp. Studies- Relations. w/ int'l organizations-Yugoslavia., 1992-1993. (Box 100, Folder 1)
- Index: X33/C6R4-Y. Organized Research-Other Organized Research-Council on Int'l & Comp. Studies- Relations. w/ int'l organizations-Yugoslavia., 1989-1991. (Box 100, Folder 2)
- Index: X33/C6R4-Y. Organized Research-Other Organized Research-Council on Int'l & Comp. Studies- Relations. w/ int'l organizations-Yugoslavia., 1988. (Box 100, Folder 3)
- Index: X33/C6R4-Y. Organized Research-Other Organized Research-Council on Int'l & Comp. Studies- Relations. w/ int'l organizations-Yugoslavia., 1986-1987. (Box 100, Folder 4)
- Index: X33/C6R4-Y. Organized Research-Other Organized Research-Council on Int'l & Comp. Studies- Relations. w/ int'l organizations-Yugoslavia., 1984. (Box 100, Folder 5)
- Index: X33/C6R4-Y. Organized Research-Other Organized Research-Council on Int'l & Comp. Studies- Relations. w/ int'l organizations-Yugoslavia., 1971-1983. (Box 100, Folder 6)
- Index: X33/C6R4-K. Organized Research-Other Organized Research-Council on Int'l & Comp. Studies- Relations. w/ int'l organizations-Korea., 1993. (Box 101, Folder 1)
- Index: X33/C6R4-K. Organized Research-Other Organized Research-Council on Int'l & Comp. Studies- Relations. w/ int'l organizations-Korea., 1992. (Box 101, Folder 2)
- Index: X33/C6R4-K. Organized Research-Other Organized Research-Council on Int'l & Comp. Studies- Relations. w/ int'l organizations-Korea., 1990-1991. (Box 101, Folder 3)
- Index: X33/C6R4-K. Organized Research-Other Organized Research-Council on Int'l & Comp. Studies- Relations. w/ int'l organizations-Korea., 1989. (Box 101, Folder 4)
- Index: X33/C6R4-K. Organized Research-Other Organized Research-Council on Int'l & Comp. Studies- Relations. w/ int'l organizations-Korea., 1987-1988. (Box 101, Folder 5)
- Index: X33/C6R4-K. Organized Research-Other Organized Research-Council on Int'l & Comp. Studies- Relations. w/ int'l organizations-Korea., 1984-1986. (Box 101, Folder 6)
- Index: X33/C6R4-K. Organized Research-Other Organized Research-Council on Int'l & Comp. Studies- Relations. w/ int'l organizations-Korea., 1982-1983. (Box 101, Folder 7)
- Index: BL4/A2. Systemwide Administration-Planning & Analysis-Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning-Coord. of Acad., Phys. & Fiscal Planning-APPRB., 1985. (Box 102, Folder 1)
- Index: BL4/A2. Systemwide Administration-Planning & Analysis-Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning-Coord. of Acad., Phys. & Fiscal Planning-APPRB., 1981. (Box 102, Folder 2)
- Index: BL4/A2. Systemwide Administration-Planning & Analysis-Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning-Coord. of Acad., Phys. & Fiscal Planning-APPRB., 1980. (Box 102, Folder 3)
- Index: BL4/A2. Systemwide Administration-Planning & Analysis-Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning-Coord. of Acad., Phys. & Fiscal Planning-APPRB., 1980. (Box 102, Folder 4)
- Index: BL4/A2. Systemwide Administration-Planning & Analysis-Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning-Coord. of Acad., Phys. & Fiscal Planning-APPRB., 1973-1978. (Box 103, Folder 1)
- Index: BL4/A2. Systemwide Administration-Planning & Analysis-Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning-Coord. of Acad., Phys. & Fiscal Planning-APPRB., 1970-1972. (Box 103, Folder 2)
- Index: BL4/M3H. Systemwide Administration-Planning & Analysis-Coordination of Acad., Phys. & Fiscal Planning-Coord. of Acad., Phys. & Fiscal Planning-Hitch., 1972-1973. (Box 103, Folder 3)
- Index: IB10/A53-Ath. Public relations-Cooperation for outside entities-Educational & profession org.-Am. Council on Educ.-Athletics., 1987-1993. (Box 103, Folder 4)
- Index: IB10/A53-Ath. Public relations-Cooperation for outside entities-Educational & profession org.-Am. Council on Educ.-Athletics., 1985. (Box 103, Folder 5)
- Index: IB10/A53-Ath. Public relations-Cooperation for outside entities-Educational & profession org.-Am. Council on Educ.-Athletics., 1983. (Box 103, Folder 6)
- Index: IB10/A53-Ath. Public relations-Cooperation for outside entities-Educational & profession org.-Am. Council on Educ.-Athletics., 1983. (Box 104, Folder 1)
- Index: IB10/A53-Ath. Public relations-Cooperation for outside entities-Educational & professional org.-Am. Council on Educ.-Athletics., 1983. (Box 104, Folder 2)
- Index: J13/F4. Governmental Relations-United States-Special Ass't to UC President-Fed. Public Works Act of 1976., 1976-1982. (Box 104, Folder 3)
- Index: J13/F4. Governmental Relations-United States-Special Ass't to UC President-Fed. Public Works Act of 1976. (Box 104, Folder 4)
- Index: P03. Academic and Staff Personnel-Campaigns and Drives-General., 1984-1992. (Box 104, Folder 5)
- Index: P03. Academic and Staff Personnel-Campaigns and Drives-General., 1962-1983. (Box 104, Folder 6)
- Index: P03/B55. Academic and Staff Personnel-Campaigns and Drives-Blood Drive., 1974-1989. (Box 104, Folder 7)
- Index: P03/B55. Academic and Staff Personnel-Campaigns and Drives-Blood Drive., 1971. (Box 105, Folder 1)
- Index: P03/U5. Academic and Staff Personnel-Campaigns and Drives-United Crusade., 1986-1994. (Box 105, Folder 2)
- Index: P03/U5. Academic and Staff Personnel-Campaigns and Drives-United Crusade., 1975-1979. (Box 105, Folder 3)
- Index: P03/U5. Academic and Staff Personnel-Campaigns and Drives-United Crusade., 1970-1974. (Box 105, Folder 4)
- Index: P03/U5Y6. Academic and Staff Personnel-Campaigns and Drives-United Crusade-Chancellor Young's participation., 1975. (Box 105, Folder 5)
- Index: X33/C6R4-I. Organized Research-Other Organized Research-Int'l Studies and Overseas Programs- Iran., 1979-1993. (Box 105, Folder 6)
- Index: X33/C6R4-I. Organized Research-Other Organized Research-Int'l Studies and Overseas Programs- Iran., 1978. (Box 105, Folder 7)
- Index: X33/C6R4-I. Organized Research-Other Organized Research-Int'l Studies and Overseas Programs- Iran., 1977. (Box 105, Folder 8)
- Index: DA69/M3. Campuswide Administration & LA Division Academic Senate-Chancellor's Office-Outside Commit-Mansfield Foundation, Activity Updates/Reports/Articles #2., 1986-1990. (Box 106, Folder 1)
- Index: DA69/M3. Campuswide Administration & LA Division Academic Senate-Chancellor's Office-Outside Commit-Mansfield Foundation, Activity Updates/Reports/Articles #1., 1984-1986. (Box 106, Folder 2)
- Index: DA69/M3. Campuswide Administration & LA Division Academic Senate-Chancellor's Office-Outside Committees-Mansfield Foundation, Fundraising #2., 1986-1988. (Box 106, Folder 3)
- Index: DA69/M3. Campuswide Administration & LA Division Academic Senate-Chancellor's Office-Outside Committees-Mansfield Foundation, Fundraising #1., 1984-1986. (Box 106, Folder 4)
- Index: DA69/M3. Campuswide Administration & LA Division Academic Senate-Chancellor's Office-Outside Committees-Mansfield Foundation, Site Selection., 1984-1986. (Box 106, Folder 5)
- Index: DA69/M3. Campuswide Administration & LA Division Academic Senate-Chancellor's Office-Outside Committees-Mansfield Foundation, Meetings #6., 1987. (Box 106, Folder 6)
- Index: DA69/M3. Campuswide Administration & LA Division Academic Senate-Chancellor's Office-Outside Committees-Mansfield Foundation, Reports #2., 1987-1993. (Box 107, Folder 1)
- Index: DA69/M3. Campuswide Administration & LA Division Academic Senate-Chancellor's Office-Outside Committees-Mansfield Foundation, Reports #1., 1985-1987. (Box 107, Folder 2)
- Index: DA69/M3. Campuswide Administration & LA Division Academic Senate-Chancellor's Office-Outside Committees-Mansfield Foundation., 1989-1992. (Box 107, Folder 3)
- Index: DA69/M3. Campuswide Administration & LA Division Academic Senate-Chancellor's Office-Outside Commit-Mansfield Foundation, Mansfield Center for Pacific Affairs., 1982-1988. (Box 107, Folder 4)
- Index: DA69/M3. Campuswide Administration & LA Division Academic Senate-Chancellor's Office-Outside Committees-Mansfield Foundation, Membership., 1980-1988. (Box 107, Folder 5)
- Index: DA69/M3. Campuswide Administration & LA Division Academic Senate-Chancellor's Office-Outside Committees-Mansfield Foundation, Programming., 1986-1987. (Box 107, Folder 6)
- Index: DA69/M3. Campuswide Administration & LA Division Academic Senate-Chancellor's Office-Outside Committees-Mansfield Foundation, Marketing/Architect Selection., 1986-1987. (Box 108, Folder 1)
- Index: DA69/M3. Campuswide Administration & LA Division Academic Senate-Chancellor's Office-Outside Committees-Mansfield Foundation, Reorganization., 1986-1987. (Box 108, Folder 2)
- Index: DA69/M3. Campuswide Administration & LA Division Academic Senate-Chancellor's Office-Outside Committees-Mansfield Foundation., 1983-1987. (Box 108, Folder 3)
- Index: DA69/M#. Campuswide Administration & LA Division Academic Senate-Chancellor's Office-Outside Committees-Mansfield Foundation, Presidential Search Committee., 1985. (Box 108, Folder 4)
- Index: S25-04. Student Associations - Board of Directors (previously Board of Control) - Constitution & Bylaws., 1970-1978. (Box 108, Folder 5)
- Index: S25-04. Student Associations - Board of Directors (previously Board of Control) - Constitution & Bylaws., 1980-1983. (Box 108, Folder 6)
- Index: S25-01. Student Associations - Board of Directors (Previously Board of Control) - Meetings., 1985-1986. (Box 108, Folder 7)
- Index: S25-01. Student Associations - Board of Directors (Previously Board of Control) - Meetings., 1986-1987. (Box 108, Folder 8)
- Index: S25-01. Student Associations - Board of Directors (Previously Board of Control) - Meetings., 1987. (Box 108, Folder 9)
- Index: JA58. Governmental Relations - United States - Executive Branch - Department of Health & Human Services - General., 1971-1987. (Box 109, Folder 1)
- Index: J25. Governmental Relations - United States - Legislative Branch - House of Representatives., 1974-1989. (Box 109, Folder 2)
- Index: J25. Governmental Relations - United States - Legislative Branch - House of Representatives., 1989-1991. (Box 109, Folder 3)
- Index: J25. Governmental Relations - United States - Legislative Branch - Congress - House of Representatives., 1989-1992. (Box 109, Folder 4)
- Index: J25. Governmental Relations - United States - Legislative Branch - House of Representatives., 1993-1995. (Box 109, Folder 5)
- Index: J22. Governmental Relations - United States - Legislative Branch - Senate., 1970-1990. (Box 109, Folder 6)
- Index: J22. Governmental Relations - United States - Legislative Branch - Congress - Senate., 1988-1994. (Box 109, Folder 7)
- Index: F25. Plant Development & Maintenance - Campus Architects & Engineers - Streets & Easements., 1971-1984. (Box 110, Folder 1)
- Index: F16. Plant Development and Maintenance - Campus Architects & Engineers - Graphics., 1972-73. (Box 110, Folder 2)
- Index: F16. Plant Development and Maintenance - Campus Architects & Engineers - Graphics., 1975-1989. (Box 110, Folder 3)
- Index: IB10-I. Public Relations - Cooperation, Aid & Information for Outside Entities - Educational & Professional Organizations & Societies - General "I"., 1987-1989. (Box 110, Folder 4)
- Index: IB10-O. Public Relations - Cooperation, Aid & Information for Outside Entities - Educational & Professional Organizations & Societies - General - "O"., 1987-1988. (Box 110, Folder 5)
- Index: X33/C6R4-J. Organized Research & Museums-Other Organized Research Programs-CICS-Relations with Int'l Organizations-Japan., 1988. (Box 111, Folder 1)
- Index: X33/C6R4-J. Organized Research & Museums-Other Organized Research Programs-CICS-Relations with Int'l Organizations-Japan., 1987. (Box 111, Folder 2)
- Index: X33/C6R4-J. Organized Research & Museums-Other Organized Research Programs-CICS-Relations with Int'l Organizations-Japan., 1987. (Box 111, Folder 3)
- Index: X33/C6R4P. Organized Research & Museums-Other Organized Research Programs-CICS-Relations with Int'l Organizations-Projects., 1978-1993. (Box 111, Folder 4)
- Index: X33/C6R4P-J. Organized Research & Museums-Other Organized Research Programs-CICS-Relations with Int'l Organizations-Projects-Japan., 1977. (Box 111, Folder 5)
- Index: X33/C6R4P-J. Organized Research & Museums-Other Organized Research Programs-CICS-Relations with Int'l Organizations-Projects-Japan., 1981-1987. (Box 111, Folder 6)
- Index: X33/C6R4-J. Organized Research & Museums-Other Organized Research Programs-CICS-Relations with Int'l Organizations-Japan., 1986. (Box 112, Folder 1)
- Index: X33/C6R4-J. Organized Research & Museums-Other Organized Research Programs-CICS-Relations with Int'l Organizations-Japan., 1986. (Box 112, Folder 2)